<resources>
    <string-array name = "comp_hints">
        
    <item>WHOSE NEW VERSION IS LOLLIPOP</item>
    <item>WHICH COMPANY RECENTLY BOUGHT MOTOROLA</item>
    <item>Which company says it might be making a SmartWig and applied for a patent for it</item>
    <item>Which computer operating system is named after Finnish programmer Linus Torvalds? </item>
    <item>Nokia came from which country?</item>
    <item>TRY LIVING WITHOUT IT</item>
    <item>Who invented scissors?</item>
    <item>NSA leaker Edward Snowden has successfully avoided capture by the U.S. government and works where now?</item>
    <item>What innovation did Apple add to the iPhone 5S?</item>
    <item> Microsoft CEO Steve Ballmer closed his last employee meeting with a song from the movie: </item>
  
    
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name = "friends_hints">
       
    <item>What name appears on the address label of Chandler and Joeys TV Guide</item>
    <item>What is the name of the neighbour who leaves everything to Monica and Rachel when he dies</item>
    <item>What is the name of the song that Phoebe sings the most?</item>
    <item>What is Chandler s middle name?</item>
    <item>Which of these friends had an iconic hairstyle? </item>
    <item>When Phoebe changed her name to Princess Consuela then what did Mike change his name to ? </item>
    <item>What did Monica s parents call her as a child?</item>
    <item>What fruit is Ross allergic to?</item>
    <item>Which famous person does Phoebe believe is her Grandfather?</item>
    <item>Who scored the winning point at ping-pong in Barbados ?</item>
      
    
    </string-array>
    
    
      <string-array name = "world_hints">
       
    <item>Place with shortest name in world , located in Sweden</item>
    <item>Only state in the world without a capital</item>
    <item>City where buildings have their own zip code</item>
    <item>A country with no rivers</item>
    <item>This festival of lights is the most popular Hindu festival</item>
    <item> Which Mediterranean island has been a source of conflict between Turkey and Greece in recent times?</item>
    <item>What is the name of the current President of Cuba?</item>
    <item>Who is the current president of Egypt?</item>
    <item> What would you pay with in Venezuela?</item>
    
   
    </string-array>
    
    
      <string-array name = "bollywood_hints">
       
    <item>Who stars along with Shahrukh Khan in Kal Ho Na Ho?</item>
    <item>Who is the leading actor in Main Hoon Na?</item>
    <item>In which movie Salman khan and Sharukh khan were brothers?</item>
    <item>Which actress often comes in both Bollywood and Hollywood movies?</item>
    <item> Name the film in which "Angar chand and Anpara" family exist.</item>
    <item> Which was the first sound feature film made in Bolywood ?</item>
    <item>Which film will see Farhan Akhtar and Vidya Balan opposite each other?</item>
    <item> Akshay Kumar s Holiday is a remake of which Tamil film?</item>
    <item>After 3 Idiots, Rajkumar Hirani and Aamir Khan come together in P.K. Who is the female lead in the film?</item>
    
    </string-array>
      
</resources>